{
    "id": "90069f83a4784e00bb1f42be06395e61",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Will you wait here ………………… .. I come back?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "unless",
                "up to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "57e8ce50068d419e85c64787494b8e46"
        },
        {
            "question": "I visit my grandparents …………………… I have time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "whenever",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8ec272b6fa644acd9937ab53236d62b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The car is parked …………………. the post office.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "in front of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "672ee616b8824968baf97ceeb3dc0fe5"
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked at a market ………………… he went to university.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "as",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "05108c9b79d7496097b67c5005bd7552"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will make a cake ………………….. I have time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "572e5c3ef7d54cf1b7177f47ee941fda"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… . he received the message, he escaped from the city.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As soon as",
                "As long as",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8569bd0281fe4750baaf5ab2ff7e3fa8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t care what job you do ………………… you are happy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as long as",
                "so long as",
                "as far as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "967b322bc7b24b6982053aa72d98676e"
        },
        {
            "question": "We must stay united ………………… .. happens.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "whatever",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "afcc9deddfb64477814dd3e966f4d60d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must finish it ………………… . you leave.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "as",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "45a2e6f4a1e148589532cbe301d8e792"
        },
        {
            "question": "He injured his toes …………………. he was working in the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "whenever",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cca214a065f548998657a30b641e84d6"
        }
    ]
}